I found something new on the internet and I wanted to try it so today's video
is spicy lingerie cosplays. I have several outfits here from Karura Club. They're all
made of PVC and I am excited to try them because I think they're really really
cute. Before I change, small disclaimer of course you're probably supposed to wear
them with no clothes underneath because it is a lot of rebutt we're on YouTube
and I don't want to risk anything so I'm going to wear these nice kids it's by a
mochi nice shiny and stretchy spandex I will put a link down in the description
text I also just can't cause anyway I will wear them beneath and for the first
look I'm just going to start and put it on top. Welcome to hell! I'm obviously a
devil and I think now you know why I'm opting to wear a catsuit underneath
because it is not much but it looks so fun! I totally love it! I mean there are a ton of
pieces to this outfit. We have the stockings, we have the warmers here, this
This bodysuit, a chain that runs around one time, these arm bracelets to attach the chain.
There is a tail, like a funny tail.
And of course the wigs, no sorry, wings, not wigs.
Flat flat. And the horns, also part of the outfit.
And it's pretty fun.
I have to say I've not worn something like this before.
I have some experience with roleplay lingerie.
But such an all PVC outfit is really fun and something different.
Also I am not used to such less fabric outfits.
Like if I were to wear a cat's head I would be super naked.
But I think especially with the catsuit it looks great.
Because now the whole look comes together from my fingers to my toes.
Fun.
I do have a discount code for Karora Club.
You will find it in the description text.
And this is the only outfit I chose myself.
Because the other outfits are chosen by my Patreon people.
By my community over there.
So let's get changed.
I'm a bunny now and if you can't tell yet there is a hood and that hood
is bunny ears I mean how cute is that
it's really adorable and it also I mean it also has a tail like a bunny tail is it a tail
Anyway, you know what I mean. It's small and poofy.
And it's really noisy when you wear the hood.
But the cool thing about the hood is that it's stuffed.
So it's really thick here and soft and squishy.
And I think together with the slightly pale lilac catsuit, it's also a nice look to contrast with the pink.
overall a really really cute outfit
it's adorable but it's also kinky
and we do have
stockings again we have these bands
that I think make a really nice booty
because they squish it a bit and these straps
I think they would look great if they were here which would work if I wouldn't wear a catsuit underneath because the catsuit is slippery
But now they slide a bit down. Anyway, it still looks good and
still nice ears
don't know if you can see the
Eyes of the bunny is basically a dead bunny because of the X eyes
So yeah
What do you think? Would you go out like that?
that being a kinky bunny I was thinking about wearing it to a Easter fetish party a few weeks
ago I didn't because it was a different dress code but I mean come on going out on Easter
on holiday like a bunny that's really cute I have another set of wings in this package and
it's their i guess signature costume because it's the one printed on the package
let's get changed i just took some pictures like this on the floor because i noticed that with
these kind of outfits girls tend to pose like this like sitting me on the floor and having like wide
hips and tights on the pictures and I tried to replicate that because I thought why not
and yeah this is another Succubus outfit I love that there is this headband with the horns and
the wings and of course I have the pink wings here and a bodysuit again stockings and gloves this
time so I wear two gloves on top of each other basically and this is like a buckle snap buckle
a carabiner I don't know anyway it's a nice cut I think it's really intricate here with the
crisscross here and the crisscross here again and all the straps and also there's a tail again
it looks a bit like a pigtail because it's curly anyway um yeah i'm going to get up now
here again in all its glory standing better view of the pigtail now
um yeah it's really nice i think it looks really great
I especially love the bed wings here on the headband these are so cute anyway I have one
last outfit and I'm going to change now it's something completely different this time
let's see final outfit this is the raven and it's less revealing although when I
I got the skirt, you see that it is still not a lot of fabric.
I think my patrons know me a bit and know what I like, so they chose the gothic outfit
on place 3, because this is like textbook gothic with all the raven feathers and cape
or skirt, whatever.
And yeah, I feel very real.
Like a princess.
And the feathers are, I don't know, a tad too much for myself.
But the good thing is they keep the stockings and the gloves in place.
Because everything is size adjustable.
I'm wearing size small, but everything itself is a bit size adjustable and elastic.
So it's great to adjust to everybody.
And also I think they're really affordable.
So check out the shop.
I will link everything in the description text.
I also have a discount code.
You can use that.
And if you want to support me further.
Check out my Patreon.
Because then you get to choose outfits like these.
For upcoming videos.
Whenever there is a possibility.
It's really hard to choose my favorite outfit.
I mean a bunny has bunny ear bonus obviously and even to make like a bunny hood it's such a cool
and quirky funny idea which I totally love but I think also the first outfit the red succubus
looked really good I think it's a tie between them then the pink succubus and then the raven
that's my order let me know yours in the comments down below also hit the subscribe button and the
like thumbs up button whatever and check out my other videos thanks to Corura for sending me
these outfits I had a lot of fun trying them out and I hope to see you in the next video
have a nice day bye